When you're logging a message in your app, you need
to determine what log level it should be displayed at.
Verbose logs should never be compiled into your app, except
during development. Debug logs are compiled in, but they're stripped
out at run time. Error, warn, and info logs are
all kept. And this is what the logging API looks
like. The first parameter is the log tag, which can
be any string that you want to identify the log message.
It's good practice to define the log tag as a
constant in your class. Usually it's the name of your class
or the app. The second parameter is the actual log
message. If we go back to monitor, we can see that
this is the log tag column and this is where
the log message is. If you click on this drop down
here you can filter the logs by log level. For example
you can click on Error to see all the error messages.
If you click on warn, you'll see all the warning
messages as well as anything more severe than that. The
same goes for the other levels. And verbose means that
you can see all the logs at all log levels.
As a PROTIP, you should avoid log spam for your sake and
the sake of other developers. The log buffer could fill up and important
error messages that you really need to see will either roll of the
logs or it will get lost in the sea of unimportant log messages.